0	1	2	3	4	5	6	7	8	9
West	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	1996-08-30	CD	B-LOC
Oval	JJ	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	I-LOC
Leicester	JJ	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	:	:	B-ORG
Chester-le-Street	NN	B-NP	B-LOC	mixed	0	1	.	.	O
The	DT	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	(	(	O
Portsmouth	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	)	)	B-ORG
Chesterfield	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	.	.	B-ORG
T.O'Gorman	JJ	B-NP	B-PER	mixed	0	1	,	,	B-MISC
Bristol	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	)	)	B-ORG
British	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	against	IN	B-MISC
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	none	0	0	Duke	NNP	O
Norfolk	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-ORG
Arundel	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	at	IN	B-ORG
Manchester	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	,	,	B-ORG
UNDER-21	NNP	B-NP	O	all	1	1	IN	IN	B-MISC
ROTOR	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	O
PANAMA	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	all	0	0	-	:	B-ORG
SANDS	NNP	I-NP	O	all	0	0	THE	NNP	B-MISC
Hands	NNS	B-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
Stone	NNP	B-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	of	IN	B-PER
Duran	JJ	B-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
Return	NN	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
of	IN	B-PP	I-MISC	none	0	0	Return	NN	I-ORG
the	DT	B-NP	I-MISC	none	0	0	of	IN	O
Macho	NNP	B-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
Camacho	NN	B-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
HONG	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
Hong	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Kong	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	Hong	NNP	I-LOC
G	NNP	I-NP	O	all	0	0	L	NNP	I-ORG
Ssangbangwool	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	-	:	B-PER
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	1	the	DT	B-LOC
National	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
Republic	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	Czech	JJ	I-LOC
YORK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	NEW	NNP	I-LOC
CHICAGO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
YORK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	NEW	NNP	I-LOC
MONTREAL	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
YORK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	NEW	NNP	I-LOC
National	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	6	CD	B-ORG
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	1	the	DT	B-LOC
Washington	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
Philadelphia	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
BellSouth	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	mixed	0	0	1993	CD	I-MISC
Nortel	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	1	former	JJ	B-LOC
Atlanta	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
Golden	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
BERLIN	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
Berlin	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Fredericks	NNS	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	Frankie	NNP	I-PER
UEFA	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
MONTE	JJ	B-NP	B-LOC	all	0	0	.	.	O
Sarajevo	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	for	IN	B-LOC
Kosevo	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
Atlanta	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
NICE	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	all	0	0	.	.	B-ORG
Nice	JJ	B-ADJP	B-ORG	first	0	0	for	IN	B-LOC
Paris	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	and	CC	B-LOC
Nice	JJ	B-ADJP	B-ORG	first	0	0	after	IN	B-LOC
Nice	JJ	B-ADJP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	O
ATALANTA	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	TO	TO	O
Milan	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	to	TO	B-LOC
serie	VB	I-VP	B-MISC	none	0	0	to	TO	O
SRI	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	all	0	0	-	:	B-ORG
World	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	Singer	NNP	I-MISC
Match	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
Comelf	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	O
Comelf	RB	B-ADVP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	O
Poland	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Warsaw	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	--	:	B-LOC
Canada	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Jones	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-PER
Jones	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Chicago	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	--	:	B-ORG
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	B-LOC
Douglas	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Douglas	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Johnson	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	with	IN	B-PER
Douglas	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Johnson	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	B-PER
London	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	B-LOC
interior	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	none	0	0	but	CC	O
Bund	NN	I-NP	O	first	0	0	September	NNP	I-MISC
London	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
U.S.	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	1	in	IN	B-LOC
Chicago	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
MO	NNP	I-NP	O	all	0	0	August	NNP	B-LOC
PMI	NNP	I-NP	O	all	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
PIBOR	NNP	I-NP	O	all	0	0	and	CC	B-LOC
MATIF	NNP	I-NP	O	all	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
U.S.	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	1	of	IN	B-LOC
Chicago	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Tokyo	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
EUROBONDS	NNS	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	.	.	O
Labour	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	U.S.	NNP	I-ORG
NSW	RB	B-ADVP	B-ORG	all	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
DNIB	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	.	.	O
DNIB	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
Boxing-Bruno	NN	B-NP	B-MISC	mixed	0	1	.	.	O
World	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	his	PRP$	B-MISC
Birmingham	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
Given	VBN	B-PP	B-PER	first	0	0	:	:	O
Dublin	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	--	:	B-LOC
Little	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
Nigeria	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
East	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	)	)	B-LOC
South	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Africa	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	South	NNP	I-LOC
Gold	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	and	CC	O
Chad	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-PER
N'Djamena	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	mixed	0	1	closed	VBN	B-LOC
Russian	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
Itar-Tass	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	mixed	0	1	.	.	O
Russian	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
Chechen	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
State	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	of	IN	B-ORG
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	none	0	0	Party	NNP	O
Europe	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
Soviet	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
Tajik	NN	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
Major-General	NNP	B-NP	O	mixed	0	1	,	,	B-PER
Layron	NN	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-MISC
Nations-sponsored	JJ	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	1	United	NNP	I-ORG
Federal	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-ORG
Yugoslavia	NNP	B-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Cofinec	NN	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	O
Budapest	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
BSE	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	(	(	B-MISC
Cofinec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Global	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	's	POS	B-MISC
Cofinec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Cofinec	JJ	B-ADJP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	O
IAS	NNP	B-NP	O	all	0	0	(	(	B-ORG
January-June	JJ	I-NP	O	mixed	0	1	the	DT	B-MISC
Cofinec	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Petofi	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	said	VBD	B-PER
Romania	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Bucharest	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	--	:	B-LOC
King	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	's	POS	B-PER
New	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	(	(	B-LOC
King	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	by	IN	B-PER
Hen	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	to	TO	B-LOC
Norodom	NNP	I-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	Prince	NNP	B-ORG
Southeast	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-LOC
Indonesian-origin	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	1	and	CC	B-PER
York	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	New	NNP	I-ORG
York	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	New	NNP	I-ORG
York	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	New	NNP	I-ORG
United	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	against	IN	B-LOC
Pan	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	a	DT	B-MISC
Green	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	's	POS	I-ORG
Tripoli-based	JJ	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	1	.	.	O
Wall	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	when	WRB	B-PER
White	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
White	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
American	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	The	DT	B-MISC
Factory	NN	B-NP	O	first	0	0	1996-08-30	CD	B-ORG
Barnett	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-PER
University	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	The	DT	O
Michigan	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
New	JJ	B-NP	O	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
U.S.	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	1	1996-08-30	CD	B-LOC
Northeastern	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	and	CC	B-LOC
World	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
California	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	The	DT	B-LOC
Los	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	after	IN	B-ORG
Angeles	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	Los	NNP	I-ORG
AIDS	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	from	IN	O
Cincinnati	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-ORG
Edward	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	at	IN	B-PER
Jones	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	D.	NNP	I-PER
St.	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	1	""""	""""	O
City	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	Kansas	NNP	I-ORG
A.G.	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	1	at	IN	B-LOC
Louis	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
State	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	all	0	1	The	DT	B-LOC
Nation	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	's	POS	O
Million	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	's	POS	O
March	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	Man	NNP	O
flight	NN	I-NP	I-MISC	none	0	0	Am	VBP	O
103	CD	I-NP	I-MISC	none	1	0	flight	NN	O
Offshore	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	I-ORG
Presidential	JJ	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	on	IN	O
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	none	0	0	League	NNP	O
RMS	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
Foreign	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	German	JJ	O
Arab-Israeli	JJ	B-NP	B-MISC	mixed	0	1	in	IN	B-LOC
Saint-Bernard	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	mixed	0	1	the	DT	B-ORG
pro-Socialist	JJ	I-NP	O	mixed	0	1	's	POS	B-MISC
Twenty-three	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	1	.	.	B-PER
Statistics	NNPS	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	O
Chicago	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
All	DT	B-NP	O	first	0	0	(	(	B-ORG
Islamic	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	(	(	B-MISC
Al-Akhbar	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	mixed	0	1	.	.	O
al-Aqsa	JJ	I-NP	B-LOC	mixed	0	1	's	POS	B-MISC
Jordan	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	from	IN	B-PER
al-Ram	JJ	I-NP	B-LOC	mixed	0	1	the	DT	B-MISC
Jordan	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	to	TO	B-PER
PRESALE	NNP	B-NP	O	all	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
1996-A	NNP	I-NP	O	all	1	1	Series	NN	I-MISC
Detroit	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	,	,	B-ORG
Bodman	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	:	:	B-PER
Longely	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	B-PER
Detroit	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	,	,	B-ORG
First	RB	B-ADVP	B-ORG	first	0	0	:	:	O
Michigan	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Detroit	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	,	,	B-ORG
J.J.	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	all	0	1	BY	NNP	B-PER
World	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	.	.	B-MISC
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
.	.	O	I-ORG	none	0	1	Bros	NNP	O
Democratic	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	of	IN	I-ORG
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Hong	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	with	IN	B-PER
European	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
Europe	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
Cotti	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	said	VBD	B-PER
THE	DT	B-NP	B-LOC	all	0	0	.	.	O
El	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	from	IN	B-LOC
Armenian	JJ	B-NP	O	first	0	0	if	IN	B-MISC
Europe	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
Onarheim	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
Pyramiden	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	and	CC	B-PER
Guangdong	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
IN	IN	B-PP	B-MISC	all	0	0	(	(	O
Hong	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Hong	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	,	,	B-PER
Hong	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	and	CC	B-PER
Wellington	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	--	:	B-ORG
JAKARTA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
PT	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	and	CC	B-LOC
REPUBLIKA	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	B-PER
Apic	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Apic	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	-	:	B-PER
Palestinian	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
self-rule	JJ	I-NP	I-ORG	none	0	1	Palestinian	JJ	O
UNITED	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
Jerusalem	NNP	B-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Palestinian	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
LA	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	all	0	0	.	.	B-ORG
Brazilian-born	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	1	by	IN	O
RUGBY	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	.	.	B-ORG
WIGAN	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
Republic	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-ORG
Ireland	NNP	B-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Alpine	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
Eschen	JJ	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
Republic	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-ORG
Ireland	NNP	B-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
N.	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	all	0	1	(	(	B-LOC
NETHERLANDS	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC	all	0	0	OF	IN	B-LOC
Tour	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	I-MISC
the	DT	B-NP	I-MISC	none	0	0	of	IN	O
Netherlands	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
BIRMINGHAM	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
Ata-ur-Rehman	JJ	B-NP	B-PER	mixed	0	1	4	CD	B-ORG
WORLD	NN	B-NP	O	all	0	0	-	:	B-MISC
World	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	(	(	B-MISC
Quigley	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	Jane	NNP	I-PER
Samokhvalova	NN	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	Svetlana	NNP	I-PER
Mazeikyte	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	Rasa	NNP	I-PER
Texas	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Central	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	League	NNP	I-ORG
Texas	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
New	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
York	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	New	NNP	I-ORG
Ex-Yankee	NNP	B-NP	O	mixed	0	1	.	.	B-LOC
Chicago	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Telgheder	NN	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	.	.	O
City	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	Kansas	NNP	I-ORG
F.P.	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	all	0	1	's	POS	B-LOC
SAN	JJ	O	B-LOC	all	0	0	BEAT	NN	B-ORG
Leicester	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	with	IN	B-ORG
Harlequins	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	at	IN	B-ORG
Bristol	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	and	CC	B-LOC
South	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Park	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	's	POS	B-LOC
East	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	:	:	B-LOC
South	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-LOC
Park	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	's	POS	B-LOC
Leeds	NNPS	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	(	(	B-ORG
Lola	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	B-PER
Lola	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	B-PER
SPRINGBOKS	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	O
SOUTH	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	all	0	0	-	:	B-MISC
North	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-ORG
YUGOSLAV	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	-	:	B-PER
Hajduk	NNS	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	A	NNP	I-PER
B	NNP	B-NP	O	all	0	0	(	(	I-ORG
)	)	O	O	none	0	1	B	NNP	I-ORG
)	)	O	I-ORG	none	0	1	L	NNP	O
)	)	O	I-ORG	none	0	1	L	NNP	O
(	(	O	I-ORG	none	0	1	Rad	NN	O
Division	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	0	CD	B-ORG
BJ	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	(	(	B-PER
N	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	(	(	O
N	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	(	(	O
BJ	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	(	(	B-PER
INCE	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	all	0	0	-	:	B-ORG
GASCOIGNE	NNP	I-NP	B-PER	all	0	0	BY	NNP	B-ORG
TROFEJ	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	-	:	B-PER
Trofej	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
BASKETBALLSOCCER	NNP	B-NP	O	all	0	0	)	)	B-ORG
TROFEJ	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	-	:	B-PER
Trofej	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
DINAMO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	BEAT	NN	B-LOC
Trofej	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
UNDER-21	NNP	B-NP	O	all	1	1	IN	IN	B-MISC
Hong	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Kong	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	Hong	NNP	I-LOC
Professional	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	O
Kong	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	Hong	NNP	I-LOC
HONG	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
Hong	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Kong	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	Hong	NNP	I-LOC
Brown	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
1993	CD	I-NP	B-MISC	none	1	0	the	DT	O
Tiger	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	.	.	O
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	1	the	DT	B-LOC
Cup	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	I-MISC
Fed	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
Fed	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	to	TO	B-ORG
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	1	the	DT	B-LOC
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	1	the	DT	B-LOC
National	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
1997	CD	I-NP	B-MISC	none	1	0	's	POS	O
U.S.	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	all	0	1	the	DT	B-LOC
World	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	:	:	B-MISC
ANGELES	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	all	0	0	LOS	NNP	I-ORG
El	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	)	)	B-ORG
YORK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	NEW	NNP	I-LOC
CHICAGO	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
YORK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	NEW	NNP	I-LOC
MONTREAL	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	-	:	B-LOC
YORK	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	all	0	0	NEW	NNP	I-LOC
National	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	2	CD	B-ORG
CINCINNATI	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	all	0	0	.	.	B-ORG
Major	JJ	B-NP	O	first	0	0	1996-08-31	NNP	B-MISC
Devon	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	and	CC	B-ORG
National	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
(	(	O	B-PER	none	0	1	saw	VBD	O
Tom	NNP	B-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	(	(	B-PER
(	(	B-LST	B-PER	none	0	1	and	CC	O
Jerry	NNP	B-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	(	(	B-PER
Montreal	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	one	CD	B-ORG
York	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	New	NNP	I-ORG
Louis	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	St	NNP	I-ORG
Colorado	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
St	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
Wall	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
National	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
Scots	NNS	I-NP	O	first	0	0	The	DT	B-MISC
German	JJ	I-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	-	:	B-MISC
1998	CD	I-NP	B-MISC	none	1	0	their	PRP$	O
World	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	1998	CD	B-MISC
division	NN	I-NP	B-MISC	none	0	0	first	JJ	O
Attendancce	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
division	NN	I-NP	B-MISC	none	0	0	first	JJ	O
KNOCK-OUT	NNP	B-NP	O	all	0	1	-	:	B-PER
The	DT	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	1996-08-31	CD	O
Netherlands	NNP	I-NP	I-LOC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-LOC
TATTERSALLS	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	-	:	B-PER
1998	CD	I-NP	B-MISC	none	1	0	AFTER	NNP	O
WORLD	NN	I-NP	I-MISC	all	0	0	1998	CD	B-MISC
U-21	NNP	B-NP	O	all	1	1	IN	IN	B-MISC
The	DT	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	O
Sunday	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	The	DT	O
Libran	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	a	DT	B-PER
Iron	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
Queen	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	-	:	B-ORG
Orleans	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-MISC
Eugene	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	Prince	NNP	B-PER
Treaty	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-ORG
Holy	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Spanish	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	of	IN	B-MISC
Transvaal	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
Red	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-ORG
Peking	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
On	IN	B-PP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
the	DT	B-NP	I-MISC	none	0	0	On	IN	O
Ice	NN	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
Alex	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	in	IN	B-PER
Lawrence	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
Anne	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
a	DT	B-NP	I-MISC	none	0	0	of	IN	O
Bishop	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	-	:	B-PER
A.J.P.	NNP	B-NP	I-PER	all	0	1	(	(	B-LOC
Taylor	NNP	B-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	)	)	B-PER
Stars	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-ORG
Holland	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
Scottish	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-MISC
STIRLING	VBG	B-VP	B-LOC	all	0	0	.	.	B-ORG
British	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	1996-08-31	NNP	B-MISC
Conservatives	NNS	B-NP	O	first	0	0	.	.	B-ORG
Prime	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	British	NNP	I-ORG
Jordan	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	,	,	B-PER
Iraqi	JJ	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
British	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
S.	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	1	of	IN	B-PER
Ssangbangwool	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	-	:	B-PER
South	JJ	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	1996-08-31	NNP	B-LOC
Northern	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
Rally	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	The	DT	O
the	DT	B-NP	I-ORG	none	0	0	for	IN	O
Return	NN	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	O
Rwanda	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
Refugees	NNS	B-NP	O	first	0	0	for	IN	B-MISC
Moslems	NNS	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	.	.	O
Urus-Martan	JJ	B-NP	B-LOC	mixed	0	1	of	IN	B-MISC
Freedom	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-ORG
Zycie	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	B-PER
Zycie	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
Zycie	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
UWP-Hachette	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	mixed	0	1	with	IN	B-LOC
Bertillon	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
In	IN	B-PP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
the	DT	B-NP	I-MISC	none	0	0	In	IN	O
January	NNP	B-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	of	IN	O
The	DT	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
The	DT	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
A	DT	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	""""	""""	O
World	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	A	DT	B-MISC
of	IN	B-PP	I-MISC	none	0	0	World	NNP	O
Things	NNS	B-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	of	IN	O
The	DT	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
A	DT	B-NP	B-MISC	all	0	0	""""	""""	O
SANTIAGO	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	all	0	0	.	.	B-LOC
United	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
New	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
China	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
Strike	NN	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
Communist	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
Islamic	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-MISC
Suu	NNP	I-NP	I-PER	first	0	0	San	NNP	I-ORG
National	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	's	POS	I-ORG
League	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	National	NNP	I-MISC
for	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	none	0	0	League	NNP	O
and	CC	I-NP	I-ORG	none	0	0	Law	NNP	O
Leo	NNP	O	I-PER	first	0	0	(	(	B-PER
Dow	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-MISC
Dow	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	The	DT	B-MISC
China	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
South	JJ	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
North	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-LOC
Korean	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	North	NNP	I-MISC
North	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
New	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
China	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
New	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
China	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
Hong	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	.	.	B-PER
High	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	O
Hong	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Kong	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	Hong	NNP	I-LOC
China	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Chuman	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	in	IN	B-PER
Kurdistan	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-ORG
U.S.-led	JJ	B-NP	B-MISC	mixed	0	1	.	.	O
Interim	NNP	I-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	U.N.	NNP	O
Lebanon	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
Sikhin	JJ	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	none	0	0	Party	NNP	O
God	NNP	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-PER
Turkish-operated	JJ	I-NP	O	first	0	1	a	DT	B-MISC
Bahraini	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	a	DT	B-MISC
Kurdistan	JJ	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-ORG
United	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	1996-08-31	NNP	B-LOC
LE	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	.	.	B-MISC
Trade	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	-	:	B-ORG
Palestinian	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
East	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
90	CD	I-NP	B-LOC	none	1	0	and	CC	O
Air	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-ORG
Motel	NNP	I-NP	O	first	0	0	Falls	NNP	I-LOC
Lilac	NNP	I-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-ORG
of	IN	B-PP	I-ORG	none	0	0	Department	NNP	O
Defense	NN	B-NP	I-ORG	first	0	0	of	IN	B-ORG
Troy	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	in	IN	I-ORG
Tennessee	NNP	B-NP	B-LOC	first	0	0	,	,	B-ORG
/	SYM	O	I-MISC	none	0	1	F	NN	O
A-18	NN	B-NP	I-MISC	all	1	1	/	SYM	O
F-14	NN	I-NP	B-MISC	all	1	1	,	,	O
Tarawa	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Carl	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	The	DT	B-PER
Liberte	JJ	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	.	.	B-MISC
ONDH	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	all	0	0	(	(	B-LOC
Der	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	told	VBD	B-PER
Nato	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	.	.	B-ORG
Fal	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	and	CC	B-PER
Michael	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
Collins	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	Michael	NNP	I-PER
Venice	NNP	I-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	the	DT	B-LOC
Irish	NNP	I-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	the	DT	B-MISC
Intelligence	NNP	B-NP	O	first	0	0	of	IN	B-ORG
Warner	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	by	IN	B-PER
The	DT	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	O
Schindler	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	""""	""""	B-PER
List	NN	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	's	POS	O
Jordan	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	in	IN	B-LOC
Collins	NNP	B-NP	B-PER	first	0	0	of	IN	B-ORG
Michael	NNP	B-NP	B-MISC	first	0	0	'	''	B-PER
Collins	NNP	I-NP	I-MISC	first	0	0	Michael	NNP	I-PER
Bangladesh	NNP	B-NP	B-ORG	first	0	0	,	,	B-LOC
